final List<Map<String, dynamic>> colorQuizQuestions = [
  {
    'question': 'What color is the sky?\nما لون السماء؟',
    'answers': ['Green', 'Blue', 'Yellow'],
    'correct': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What color are bananas?\nما لون الموز؟',
    'answers': ['Yellow', 'Red', 'Black'],
    'correct': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What color are apples?\nما لون التفاح؟',
    'answers': ['Red', 'Pink', 'Gray'],
    'correct': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What color is grass?\nما لون العشب؟',
    'answers': ['Purple', 'Green', 'Orange'],
    'correct': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What color are clouds?\nما لون السحب؟',
    'answers': ['White', 'Blue', 'Brown'],
    'correct': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What color is an orange?\nما لون ثمرة البرتقال؟',
    'answers': ['Yellow', 'Orange', 'Red'],
    'correct': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What color are strawberries?\nما لون الفراولة؟',
    'answers': ['Red', 'Black', 'Blue'],
    'correct': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What color is chocolate?\nما لون الشوكولاتة؟',
    'answers': ['Brown', 'Green', 'White'],
    'correct': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What color is milk?\nما لون اللبن؟',
    'answers': ['Black', 'White', 'Purple'],
    'correct': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What color is the sun?\nما لون الشمس؟',
    'answers': ['Yellow', 'Pink', 'Blue'],
    'correct': 0,
  },
];
